const STORE = {
questions: [
   //1
   {     
    question:"Ontario, Erie, Michigan, Huron, and Superior are each the name of...",
    options:["One of the 5 Northern Territories", "One of the 5 West Provinces", "One of the 5 Great Rivers of Canada" , "One of the 5 Great Lakes"
            ],
    answer:"One of the 5 Great Lakes",
   },
   //2
   {     
    question:"The longest river in Canada isâ€¦",
    options:["The Yukon River", "The Mackenzie River", "The Saint Lawrence River" , "The Saskatchewan River"
            ],
    answer:"The Mackenzie River",
   },
   //3
   {     
    question:"The highest mountain in Canada is...",
    options:["Mount Logan", "Mount Yellowknife", "Mount Revelstoke" , "Mont Tremblant"
            ],
    answer:"Mount Logan",
   },
   //4
   {     
    question:"Canada is surrounded by all of the following oceans accept...",
    options:["The Arctic Ocean", "The Greenland Ocean", "The Pacific Ocean" , "The Atlantic Ocean"
            ],
    answer:"The Greenland Ocean",
   },
   //5
   {     
    question:"The largest forest region in Canada is called the...",
    options:["Acadian Forest Region", "Columbia Forest Region", "Boreal Forest Region" , "Subalpine Forest Region"
            ],
    answer:"Boreal Forest Region",
   },
   //6
   {     
    question:"In Tofino British Columbia, you are most likely to find people participating in which of the following recreational activities?",
    options:["Mountain Biking", "Bird Watching", "Surfing" , "All of the Above"
            ],
    answer:"All of the Above",
   },
   //7
   {     
    question:"Which of the following is the second biggest city in Canada by population?",
    options:["Vancouver", "Calgary", "Montreal" , "Halifax"
            ],
    answer:"Montreal",
   },
   //8
   {     
    question:"The population of the Greater Toronto Area as of the 2016 Census is estimated to be closest to...",
    options:["4.5 Million People", "5.5 Million People", "6.5 Million People" , "7.5 Million People"
            ],
    answer:"6.5 Million People",
   },
   //9
   {     
    question:"The name of the highest waterfall in Canada is?",
    options:["James Bruce Falls", "Athabasca Falls", "Niagara Falls" , "Saint Anne Falls"
            ],
    answer:"James Bruce Falls",
   },
   //10
   {     
    question:"What is the name of the largest lake by area, wholly in Canada?",
    options:["Great Slave Lake", "Lake Superior", "Lake of the Woods" , "Lake Ontario"
            ],
    answer:"Great Slave Lake",
   }
],
currentQuestion: 0,
score: 0
};